《絕命律師》前請提要
Previously, on "Better Call Saul."
梅薩維德銀行的業務拉得好
Good job with Mesa Verde!
我在這家律所有前途嗎
Do I have a future with this firm?
我會跟霍華德談談
I'll talk to Howard.
跟我來
Come with me.
你要干什么
What are you gonna do?
相信我
Trust me.
維克多  中間是"K"
Viktor, with a "K."
這位迷人的女士呢
And this lovely lady?
吉賽爾  吉賽爾·圣·克萊爾
Giselle... Giselle St. Claire.
你要去做證嗎
You gonna have to testify?
我的錢包在他口袋里  再加上那把槍
My wallet in his pocket, add the gun,
他得蹲個五到十年了
he gets a 5 to 10 stretch.
我希望你能告訴警方
I would like for you to tell the police
槍是你的
that the gun was yours.
那我就要面臨非法持槍的指控了
No, I'd be subject to the gun charge.
再也不必踏遍世界
Now you don't have to search the world
尋找完美的禮物啦
for the perfect gift.
傳統工藝  手工制作
Handmade in the tradition of ancient artists...
-長草娃娃  -全新長草娃娃寵物
- Ch-ch-ch-chia! - ...It's new chia pets!
長草象娃娃  牛娃娃  還有小獅崽
Chia elephant, chia cow, and chia lion cub.
步驟簡單
It's easy.
將長草娃娃在水里泡一晚  撒上種子...
Soak your chia overnight, spread the seeds...
點名
...Call roll.
阿卡先生
Mr. Aka.
磯鷂渡生活協助中心
...Resident of a Sandpiper Crossing facility
或是其他類似退休社區的居民
or similar retirement community,
你也許有資格獲得補償
you may be eligible to receive compensation.
磯鷂渡生活協助中心
Residents of some Sandpiper Crossing
或其他類似退休社區的部分居民
or similar retirement communities
可能因基礎商品和服務被超額收費
may have been overcharged for goods and services.
與哈姆林麥吉爾聯合律所合作
In partnership with the law offices of Hamlin, Hamlin & Mcgill,
戴維斯梅因律所致力于幫助
the law offices of Davis & Main are working to help those
被退休社區超額收費的居民
who have been overcharged by their retirement communities.
如需免費咨詢
For your free consultation,
請撥打戴維斯梅因律所505-242-7700
Call Davis & Main at 505-242-7700.
505-242-770...
That's 505-242-770...
絕命律師
第二季 第六集
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
翻譯  TheWalkingNerd  喵球球  自然卷
翻譯  joy_bwl  酸奶  西陵折枝
校對  喃喃
時間軸   姜姜  夢龍
后期 daylight小新  總監  喃喃
打開微信   掃描左側二維碼
或搜索公眾號:    美劇炸了
了解最新影視資訊字幕信息
這是金·韋克斯勒的語音信箱  請留言
You've reached Kim Wexler. Please leave a message.
*某天你會看見我*
*Someday, you'll see me*
*漂浮在燦爛陽光里*
*Floatin' in the sunshine*
*低飛的云朵里我探出頭*
*My head stickin' out from a low-flyin' cloud*
*你會聽見我呼喚*
*You'll hear me call you*
*歌聲穿透陽光*
*Singin' through the sunshine*
*甜美清澈至極*
*Sweet and clear as can be*
*巴里海輕聲細語*
*Bali ha'i will whisper*
音樂劇《南太平洋》中的神秘島嶼"巴里海"
*乘著海洋之風*
*on the winds of the sea*
*我在這兒  你的獨特島嶼*
*Here am I, your special island!*
*到這兒來  到這兒來*
*Come to me, come to me!*
*巴里海  巴里海*
*Bali ha'i, bali ha'i*
*巴里海*
*Bali ha'i*
好啦  就這樣
All right, there you go.
為期一周的《南太平洋》音樂劇巡演到此為止
That completes our weeklong tour of "South Pacific."
不客氣
You're welcome.
明天我們開始探索
Tomorrow we begin our exploration
卡朋特樂隊的曲目
of The Carpenters' catalogue.
當然我也接受點歌  沒錯
Of course, I'm open to requests. That's right.
你只需要撥電話給我  隨時歡迎
All you got to do is call me, any time.
好嗎
All right?
再見
Uh...Bye.
打給我
Call me.
注意界限  阮女士
Boundaries, Mrs. Nguyen.
注意界限
Boundaries.
你在這兒干嘛  飯碗這么快就搞丟啦
Why are you here? You lose that job already?
我最好有那么幸運
I should be so lucky.
你不喜歡你的工作嗎
You don't like your job?
可憐的孩子
Boo-hoo. Poor baby.
你可知道有些人忙于生計
You know, ‭some people work for a living.
可沒人派給我們免費用車
No one gives us free cars.
-你到底來這做什么  -我付了這兒房租
- So why are you here?  - This place is paid up.
身為合法房客我有權利待在這
I'm within my rights as your legal tenant.
你只需要知道這點
That's all you need to know.
是咖啡香嗎  你在煮咖啡嗎
Do I smell coffee? Have you got a pot on?
怎么
Why?
幫我來一杯如何
How about a fill-up?
你自己買得起
You can afford to buy your own.
咖啡越早來  我就越快走
Faster I get coffee, the faster I'm out of here.
你好  女士們
Chào các cô, ladies!
該死的...
Son of a...
日間美容美甲
金柏莉·韋克斯勒
你東西還沒有整理好
You haven't unpacked yet?
凱文和佩奇到了
Kevin and Paige are here.
沒問題
Absolutely.
我不清楚查克具體跟你說了什么
I don't know exactly what Chuck may have said to you,
但你要知道
but just so you know,
我并沒有要求他幫我說話
I did not ask him to step in on my behalf.
你們好  抱歉久等
Hi, guys. Sorry for the wait.
-沒關系  -你好
- Not a problem. - ‭Hi.
很高興再次見到你
Wonderful to see you again.
-霍華德  -凱文
- Howard. - ‭Kevin.
你好  金  很高興見到你們倆
Hi, Kim. ‭Good to see you two.
你好  佩琪  你好  凱文
Hi, Paige. Hi, Kevin.
金  很高興見到你
Kim, ‭great to see you.
-請坐  -謝謝
- Please, have a seat. - ‭Thank you.
凱文  你孫子怎么樣了
Kevin, how's your grandson?
管不住啊
Oh, outta control,
圍著我們團團轉
just running circles around all of us.
你好  有什么事嗎
Hello. Can I help you?
你知道我為什么來嗎
You know why I'm here?
他需要你的答復
He needs an answer.
不好意思  我不得不拒絕
Respectfully, ‭I'm gonna have to say no.
你確定嗎
You sure about that?
確定
I am.
歡迎
法官大人  被告的請求很合理
Your honor, the defense has made the very reasonable request
請求原告公開醫療記錄
that the plaintiffs produce their medical records
健康保險流通與責任法案
或已簽字的HIPPA授權書
or, barring that, a signed HIPAA release
以便我方自行檢查記錄
so that we can examine the records ourselves.
法官大人  我方委托人的醫療記錄
Your honor, ‭our clients' medical records
與此案內在是非毫無關聯
have no bearing ‭on the merits of this case.
醫療記錄與此案關聯顯著
The medical records are plainly relevant,
因為它們與我方觀點聯系緊密
as they bear directly on our contention that
即這些原告人并不能充分代表集體訴訟
the plaintiffs are not adequate class representatives.
這顯然是想脅迫原告人
This is a transparent attempt at intimidation.
-僅此而已  -為什么
- Nothing more. - ‭How so?
我方委托人的醫療記錄里
Many of our clients have information
大多都有不愿公開的隱私信息
in their medical records that they prefer to keep private.
他們和我們一樣害怕
They're fearful, as any of us would be,
一群陌生人
at the thought of a bunch of strangers
偷看他們的私人資料
poking around ‭in their personal files,
如果強迫他們公開這部分信息
and by forcing them to reveal this information,
被告就是在脅迫他們撤訴
the defense is banking on them simply dropping out of the case.
法官大人  這只是集體訴訟確認而已
Your honor, this is about class certification. That's all.
如果名單中的原告人患有癡呆
If the named plaintiffs are suffering from dementia
或其他精神缺陷
or other mental deficiencies --
你是說他們沒有行為能力嗎
you're saying they're incompetent?
我是說為了集體訴訟確認
I'm saying we have the right to any record
我們有權獲得證明原告
that would speak to their competency,
具備行為能力的任何資料
as regards this class-certification issue.
法官大人  被告方似乎想兩者兼得
Your honor, it seems that the defense wants to have it both ways, then.
如果我方委托人患有癡呆
If our clients ‭are suffering from dementia,
那么他們最初和磯鷂渡簽署住宿合同時
then the residency contracts they signed with Sandpiper
就不可能是知情的
couldn't have been entered into knowingly.
不不  我們不是這個意思
No, no. That is not what we're...
被告想聲稱
The defense wants to claim
居住者有能力簽署合同
that their residents are competent enough to be held to their contracts
卻沒有能力起訴
but too incompetent to sue.
這不是很矛盾嗎
So which is it?
許多居住者是很多年前簽署合同的
Many of the residents signed their contracts years ago,
那時候他們完全有行為能力
and at the time, ‭they were perfectly competent.
但這是會變的
But that can change,
尤其是年歲已高的居住者
especially when we're talking about elderly individuals.
那么也許磯鷂渡專挑有精神疾病的老年人
Or maybe sandpiper preyed on mentally incompetent seniors
騙走了他們的錢財
and bilked them out of their money.
韋克斯勒小姐
Miss Wexler.
我只是在為我方委托人辯護
I am simply trying to defend our clients
免受被告方欺壓
from bullying by the defense.
法官大人  正如您面前的報告中所述
Your honor, as stated in the brief in front of you,
這是個標準申請
this is a standard request,
在同類案件中均被允許
granted in every case of its kind.
這不是欺壓
This is not about bullying.
允許這樣的隱私侵犯
Granting this invasion of privacy
會讓我們的委托人二次受害
allows our clients to be doubly victimized.
我請求拒絕被告的動議  法官大人
I ask that you deny the defense's motion, your honor.
我傾向于允許這一申請
I'm leaning toward granting the motion,
但我想重讀一下訴狀和簡述
but I would like to review the pleadings and briefs again.
我會很快答復你們
I'll have my decision for you shortly.
休庭
Adjourned.
回辦公室再見
I'm gonna meet you back at the office.
韋克斯勒小姐  你好
Ms. Wexler. Hey.
我只想說  你剛才表現很好
I just wanted to say, good work in there.
謝謝  但我肯定輸了
Thanks, but I -- I'm pretty sure I lost.
當然了  這種情況你贏不了的
Oh, of course you did. It's an unwinnable position.
所以你上司都懶得出面
That's why your boss didn't bother showing up.
但是你堅持不懈  雖敗猶榮  我很欣賞
But you went down swinging, and I admire that.
謝謝
Thank you.
你午餐有什么安排
What are you doing for lunch?
可能就在自動販賣機買點吧
Um, probably just grabbing something from the vending machines.
我們可以吃好一點嘛
We can do better than that.
斯韋卡特先生  很高興見到你
Mr. Schweikart, good to see you, sir.
-你好嗎  肖恩  -我很好
- Ah, how you doing, Sean? ‭- Very well.
要什么喝的  您還是要莫斯科之騾嗎
Can I get some drinks for you two? Your usual Moscow Mule?
肯定的  你要嗎
Absolutely. You want one?
全市最好的莫斯科之騾
Best Moscow Mule in the city.
新鮮的生姜  純銅杯  很正宗
Fresh ginger, ‭real copper mug, the works.
真是復古  我不用了
That's very vintage, but I'm good.
冰茶就可以了
Just an iced tea.
你確定嗎
You sure?
那好吧  我就獨自做一個
All right, then. I'll be the sole degenerate
工作日中午喝酒的墮落漢吧
who's drinking ‭in the middle of a work day.
那也是復古了
That, too, is vintage.
我去讓他們調
I'll get those started.
所以你在哈姆林麥吉爾聯合律所十年了
So, you've been with HHM, what -- 10 years?
沒錯  去年八月滿十年
Y-yeah, last August.
你是從收發室做起的嗎
And you started in the mail room?
沒錯  我在那干了六年
I did. I was six years there.
你怎么知道的
How did you know that?
我問別人的  這地方很小
Oh, I asked around. It's a small town.
聽上去你已經盡職盡責了
You know, it sounds like you certainly paid your dues.
我運氣很好
I was very fortunate.
律所一邊讓我工作  一邊供我讀完法學院
HHM put me through law school while I worked.
他們很會培養人才
That's great that ‭they foster talent like that.
現在你給他們工作  就當還債是吧
And I imagine you're paying it off as part of your deal?
是的  我很樂意
Yeah, happily.
好多人都是這樣的安排
It's a pretty standard arrangement.
我得說  今天看你在法庭上
I have to say, ‭watching you in court today,
確實勾起我不少回憶
it sure did bring back some old memories for me.
反正讓我想起了一件事
One in particular, anyway.
-是嗎  -是的
- Yeah? - ‭Yeah.
我當時從法學院畢業一年  在波士頓一家律所
I was a year out of law school at this firm in Boston,
我終于接了第一個大案子
and I was finally put on my first big case --
一樁大型就業歧視案
This huge ‭employment-discrimination suit.
這案子讓律所十年都有活干
That thing kept us in billing for a decade.
總之  我們接了這單大的
Anyway, we landed this monster,
而且我成為了預審聽證時
and I find out I'm second chair to one of the partners
一位合伙人的助理律師
on the preliminary hearing,
我就想  "就是它了
and I think, "This is it.
"我之后的職業生涯全靠這一搏了"
"This is what will define the rest of my career."
聽證會越來越近
So, the hearing's getting closer and closer,
我甚至買了一件負擔不起的西裝
I even get this new suit that I can't afford --
我分三張信用卡刷的
I split it over three credit cards.
可能現在還在還錢
I'm probably still paying it off to this day.
我一大早就去了  穿著我的新西裝
So, I go in bright and early, I'm wearing my new suit,
準備桌上的材料  這時抗辯方走進來
prepping my table, and in walks the opposing counsel.
他們有四個人  一個高級合伙人
There's four of them -- one senior partner
還有三個高級律師
and three high-level associates.
我還沒出生他們就干這行了
These guys have been litigating longer than I've been alive.
但我想的是  "我很優秀
But I think, "Mm, I'm good.
"我老板來了就沒事了"
"I got my boss coming. It'll be fine."
我就一個人坐在桌前
So, I'm sitting alone, at my table,
等著老板現身
waiting for my boss to show.
我等啊等
And I'm waiting.
等啊等
突然  他們宣布開庭
And then, suddenly, ‭they're calling us to order,
我才意識到我的律所沒人來
and I realize that no one from my firm is coming.
只有我一個
It's just me.
我心想  "好吧
So I think, "All right, then.
"是時候了"
"This is the moment."
我上前拼了老命地辯論
And I get up there, and I argue like my life depended on it.
汗流浹背  旁征博引
I'm sweating, and I'm citing statutes left and right.
我表現得還行
And I'm doing okay. Respectable.
但我這把BB槍難敵四架榴彈炮
But I'm just a BB gun to these four howitzers.
我當然輸了
And I lose, of course.
這不可避免
It was inevitable.
但之后我突然意識到
But later, it hit me
我的老板根本就沒打算到場
that my boss never intended to show.
他們都一笑而過
And they all laughed about it.
拍著我背說  那是對我的考驗
They patted me on the back, said it was my trial by fire,
我也跟他們一起笑  但你知道
and I laughed with them, but, you know,
我覺得很不好受
It never really sat well with me.
你需要他們的支持
You want them to have your back.
因為最后我才知道
Because at the end of the day,
那不是為了考驗我的勇氣
it wasn't about proving my mettle.
而是我老板不想錯過高爾夫
My boss had a tee time that he didn't want to miss.
我在那兒沒待多久
I wasn't there long.
可以問下你為什么叫我...來這嗎
Could I ask why we... are here?
我已經注意你很久了
You know, I've had my eye on you for a while.
自從凱特爾曼一案開始
Since that Kettleman thing.
你真是為他搞定了一樁極好的案子
That was an excellent deal you got for him.
我想知道為什么
And I'm wondering why someone
一個可以搞定那一單的人
who could put together a deal like that
沒有后援  明知要輸  卻還要辯護
is arguing a losing position with no backup.
我對哈姆林麥吉爾聯合律所沒有怨言
I have no complaints about HHM.
很好
That's great.
然而  如果你碰巧正在尋求改變
However, if on the off chance, if you're pondering a change,
斯韋卡特考科利會很樂意
Schweikart and Cokely would be more than happy
善用你的才華
to put your talents to good use.
當然我們得有更正式的會面
Of course, we'd have to have a more formal meeting,
討論細節  但我們認為你會非常合適
work out specifics, but we think you would be a great fit.
我受寵若驚
Well, I'm -- I'm flattered,
但這明顯存在職業道德問題
but there's clearly an ethical issue here.
當然是等你弄完磯鷂渡的案子
Well, of course, ‭we'd take you off Sandpiper.
你放心
And rest assured,
我們不想要哈姆林麥吉爾聯合律所的
we wouldn't be expecting any information
任何策略信息
about HHM strategy.
我們是一家大規模多元化的律所
Look, we're a large, diversified firm.
想想你可以用我們的資源做什么
And just think what you can do with our resources
可以自由地展翅翱翔
and the freedom ‭to really spread your wings.
這...
That's...
我虧欠哈姆林麥吉爾聯合律所很多
I owe a lot to HHM.
學費債務嗎  我們可以替你償還
Your tuition debt? ‭We can take care of that.
真慷慨
That's very generous.
花點時間去考慮一下
Well, give it some time to think about it.
你來電話  我們就安排會面
And you give me a call, and we'll set up a meeting
會見其他高級合伙人
with the rest of the senior partners.
先說清楚...
And to be clear...
我說的可是合伙人機會
I'm talking partner track.
天哪肖恩  你是在莫斯科調的酒嗎
Jesus, Sean, what -- what'd you have to send to Moscow?
抱歉讓您久等了  斯韋卡特先生
Sorry for the wait, Mr. Schweikart.
可以點餐了嗎
Are we ready to order?
...梅斯向您推薦這款快速切菜機
...Mays here for the gourmet quick chop.
它可以十分快捷  簡便  安全地
It's the fastest, easiest, and safest way
將蔬菜切碎或切塊
to chop, mince, or dice any vegetable, guaranteed.
操作方法如下
Here's how it works.
放好蔬菜
Just place the vegetable on the board,
按下按鍵
give it tap
立刻就有了做沙拉用的細細切碎的卷心菜
and you've got finely shredded cabbage in a second for crunchy coleslaw.
再按一下...
tap again and chop...
趴下
Get down. ‭
Get down.
要帶什么話
What's the message?
收下那五千塊
Take the $5,000.
這么一句話需要兩個人來跟我說
It took two guys to tell me that?
我們只是來嚇嚇你  僅此而已
We were just supposed to scare you, that's all.
那下次更狠一點
You try harder next time.
滾出去
Get out.
滾
Get out!
朱莉  進來吧
Oh, hey, Julie. Come on in.
我這有一些磯鷂渡的文件
I've got ‭those Sandpiper documents.
好  先放這吧
Great. Just put them anywhere.
霍華德說需要你立刻處理
Howard asked if you could go through them now.
已經一點一刻了  我正要去吃午飯
It's 1:15. I was just about to grab some lunch.
兩點半之前要處理好  他要用來起草文件
Yeah, he needs them done by 2:30 so he can draft a letter.
我帶來了這個
I brought these.
我可以用備用金幫你點個外賣
Figured I could petty-cash a lunch order for you.
我得到財務的許可了  能從那家新沙拉店點餐
I got accounting to approve that new fancy salad place.
凱莉
Kaylee!
過來  別離泳池邊太遠
Come on, ‭not too far from the side.
把球丟過來  爺爺
Throw the ball, pop-pop!
我們什么時候回家
When are we going home?
怎么了  你不喜歡這里嗎
What? You don't like it here?
還好吧
It's okay.
"還好"
"It's okay"?
你有個泳池呢  你還想要什么
You got a pool. What more do you want?
-我想想  -你想想
- I guess. - ‭You guess?
你想想
You guess?
你想出來嗎
Well, you want to come out of there?
不  我要待在水里
No! I'm staying.
你想讓我進去抱你上來嗎
Well, you want me ‭to come in there and get you?
我可不能讓你待在"還好"的池子里
I can't have you in a pool that's only okay.
很好  泳池很好
It's good, it's good!
你確定嗎
You sure?
你確定
確定
I'm sure.
凱莉  寶貝  該出來了
Kaylee, honey, ‭it's time to come out now.
就再待一會兒
Just a few more minutes.
不行  聽爺爺的話
No, you do what pop-pop says.
上來吧  寶貝
Come on, baby.
免得皮膚給泡皺了
Before you turn into a prune.
小姐
Miss?
那位先生讓我告訴您
The gentleman ‭would like me to let you know
下一杯他請
that your next drink is on him.
您要點單了就叫我
Just let me know when you're ready.
我現在點
I'm ready.
不知道這招會管用
Wasn't sure that was gonna work.
別告訴我這是你第一次這樣做
Don't tell me that's the first time you've done that.
那么  你用這杯酒作投資
So, what kind of return on investment
想得到什么樣的回報呢
are you getting on these drinks?
什么都不如你
None as pretty as you.
天哪
Oh, man.
我是戴爾
I'm Dale, by the way.
吉賽爾
Giselle.
第四十四項
Okay, item number 44.
是什么
What do we have?
阿比蓋爾·希爾德雷思的居住合同
Residency contract for Abigail Hildreth.
阿比蓋爾·希爾德雷思
Abigail Hildreth.
什么時候簽的
And what's the date on that?
一九九九年八月一日
Dated August 1, 1999.
August 1, 1999.
一九九九年八月一日
有希爾德雷思女士的相應證詞嗎
And do we have the corresponding deposition for Mrs. Hildreth?
有
Yes.
你沒聽過那句話嗎
Have you ever heard the expression
"心急水不開"
"A watched pot never boils"?
在這呢
Oh. Here it is.
謝謝  看到沒
Thank you. See?
歸到第十二項了
I've got her down as item 12.
作證日期  九月十五日
Date of depo, September 15th.
九月十五日
September 15th.
15th of September.
九月十五日
September 15th.
沒錯就是九月十五日
Or, yeah, September 15th.
謝謝
Thank you.
第四十五項
Okay, item number 45.
吉米
Jimmy.
是我奶奶
Oh, it's my grandma.
她年紀大了
She's old.
我馬上回來
Be right back.
金
Kim?
你最快什么時候能趕到城里
How fast can you get downtown?
圣達菲城里嗎
Uh, Santa Fe Downtown?
-阿爾布開克  -為什么
- Albuquerque. ‭- Why?
我在旋轉餐廳的酒吧
I'm at the bar at Forque.
我釣到一條大魚了
And I've got a live one on the hook.
我馬上來
I'm on my way.
機會有多大
What's the shot?
絕對就兩三個
Definitely two or three.
你覺得他們做不到嗎
You don't think they do?
-你知道...  -他們行的
- Well, you know -- - ‭They could.
但是他們沒必要啊
I know, ‭but they don't have to. ‭
我們知道
We get it.
的確有可能
It's possible,
但我不明白這有什么大不了的
but I don't understand why that's an issue.
-是啊  是啊  -總會出亂子的
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. - It can always go bad.
是啊  是啊
Yeah, yeah. ‭
-維克多  你來  -抱歉我遲到了
- Oh, Viktor, there you are. - So sorry I'm late.
-我剛好有急事  -不用介意
- I had to put out a few fires. - ‭Not a problem.
我交了個新朋友  戴爾  這是我哥哥維克多
I made a new friend. Dale, my brother, Viktor.
-你好嗎  -很高興認識你  戴爾
- Hey, how ya doing? - Oh, nice to meet you, Dale.
-謝謝你陪我妹妹  -不客氣
- Thanks for ‭keeping sis company. - My pleasure.
你需要喝一杯
You need a drink.
來給你叫一杯
Let's get you a drink.
你是干什么的  戴爾
So, what do you do, Dale?
我是一名工程師
I'm an engineer.
美國鐵路工人  被譽為"勇敢的工程師"
就像凱西·瓊斯那樣的嗎  戴帽子
What, like Casey Jones, with the hat and...
不  傻蛋
No, idiot!
他是那種工程師  不是那種
An engineer engineer, not an "engineer."
戴爾是建東西的
Dale builds things.
我設計東西  主要是溢洪道和排水區域
I design things -- spillways and drainage fields, mostly.
其實都不是我造的
I don't -- I don't actually build them.
很厲害啊
Well, that's cool, yeah.
但你還是能戴那種帽子的吧
But you could still wear the hat, though, right?
沒有什么能阻止你吧
I mean, nothin stoppin' ya.
是啊  應該可以
Oh, yeah, I guess I could.
據我所知  沒有規定禁止你戴吧
I'm just saying, there's no rule about that, as far as I know.
你真是討厭  怎么心情這么好
Hey, you're such a brat. Why the good mood?
今天...很順利嗎
Did it... go well today?
告訴我很順利
Please tell me it went well.
是啊  很順利
Yeah, it went well.
非常順利嗎  非常非常...
Very well? Like, very, very...?
遠遠超出我們的預期...
Beyond our wildest, uh...
太好了
Yeah.
她到底喝了幾杯
How many of these has she had?
我才剛開始呢  寶貝
Mm! I am just getting started, baby.
-記住這兩張臉  戴爾  -吉賽爾
- Remember these faces, Dale. - ‭Giselle.
我們將會亮相《財富》雜志一月封面
They are gonna be on the cover of Fortune magazine, January issue.
吉賽爾  別說了
‭Giselle, please.
不  戴爾是好人  沒有惡意
No, Dale's a good guy. He's not gonna do anything.
-你讓人家覺得無聊了  -不不不  沒有
- Yeah, ‭you're boring the man. - Oh, no, no, not really.
謝謝
Thank you.
好吧  我要去一趟廁所
All right, I am off to the little girl's room.
我不在的時候不準說我壞話
Say only nice things about me while I'm gone, okay?
她真漂亮
She's something.
是啊
Yeah.
吉賽爾告訴我你們倆在創業
So, Giselle was telling me you two are starting a business.
她到底怎么和你說的
What exactly did she tell you?
沒說太多
Oh, nothing much.
就說了什么網站
Just something about a dot com,
讓人們通過互聯網交友
some way for people to hook up with each other using the internet?
聽著  我相信你是個好人
Oh, look, I'm sure you're a nice guy,
但她其實是亂說的
but she was talking out of school.
-我們...這個項目人滿了  -好吧
- We're -- we're full up on this thing. - ‭Oh. Oh, okay.
我們再簽下一名投資商
We sign one more investor,
就該上市了  我只是...
we got to go public, and I'm just...
不
No.
我們人已經滿了
We cannot take anyone else on.
無意冒犯
No offense.
沒關系
Oh, it's okay. Yeah.
不用擔心
No worries.
張開手臂
Spread your arms.
他戴了竊聽器嗎
沒有
No.
沒有竊聽器  但...
他有一把槍
He's got a gun.
我不在乎槍
I don't care about the gun.
明天  你去找地檢官
Tomorrow, ‭you go to the district attorney,
向他解釋我侄子的槍是你的
and you explain to him that my nephew's gun was yours.
地檢會問你
The D.A. will ask you,
"你為什么之前不說"
"Why you didn't say anything before?"
你跟他說你忘了  你嚇壞了...
You tell him you forgot, you were rattled --
隨便你編什么理由
Make up anything you want.
我不在乎
I don't give a shit.
但這是你的槍
But it's your gun.
我們來談談我的報酬吧
Let's discuss my payment.
晚了
Mm, that time is past.
五千塊飛了
No $5,000 for you.
我要五萬
The price is $50,000.
報酬是活著出去怎么樣
How about the payment is you get to live?
不夠
Not enough.
你覺得你有資格跟我談條件嗎
Oh, you think ‭you can negotiate with me?
只要我一句話
I say the word,
我的侄子們就會去汽車旅館
my nephews go to a certain motel,
拜訪你的兒媳
pay a visit to your daughter-in-law
和你的小孫女
and your little granddaughter.
你覺得接下來會怎么樣
What do you think happens then?
好好考慮考慮你的處境
Consider your position carefully.
要么給我錢
I get my money...
要么我們倆都別想活著走出這里
or neither of us walk out of here.
你為了這個連命都不要了嗎
You willing to die for this?
或許我比你更需要那五萬塊吧
Maybe I need the $50,000 more than you do.
我早說了吧
夠膽兒
你說話這么欠是怎么活到現在的
How you manage to live so long with a mouth like that, hmm?
五萬塊
$50,000.
槍是你的
And the gun is yours.
他派你來的嗎
He sent you?
我主動要來的
I volunteered.
只有這樣說話才安全
Only safe way for us to talk.
你剛才在那太得寸進尺了
You really pushed it in there.
我們干的那事
That thing we did...
一旦被他發現  我們倆都必死無疑
...he finds out, we're both dead.
這你清楚的吧
You get that, right?
我們干什么了
What thing we did?
這是干嘛
What's this?
兩萬五
$25,000.
為什么要給我
What for?
我們達成了協議
We made a deal.
而我搞砸了
I didn't hold up my end.
你的麻煩很快就要出來了  比我們預計的更快
Your problem is coming back sooner than we expected.
克拉多克海事銀行
大北極公司
你要把錢提出來嗎
You gonna cash that?
我認識個人  他或許能幫忙
I might know a guy who can help.
還是把它當成紀念品吧
It's better as a souvenir.
我以為你今天早上可能會  我也不知道
I figured you'd be maybe -- I don't know --
稍微開心一點
a touch happier this morning.
就算只有那么一點點
Maybe a smidge, possibly?
我很開心  非常開心
I am. I'm totally happy.
為什么會不開心
Why wouldn't I be?
我
I, uh...
我收到了一個工作邀請
I had a job offer.
真的嗎  哪家律所
Really? From where?
斯韋卡特考科利
Schweikart and Cokely.
真的假的
Seriously?
里奇·斯韋卡特甚至還說愿意幫我償還
Rich Schweikart said that they would even pay off
法學院的貸款
my law-school loans.
太棒了
That's great.
你向霍華德辭職的時候請叫上我
Please let me be there when you tell Howard.
拜托了
Please.
那為什么還一臉憂傷
So why the sad puppy eyes?
你不想要那個工作嗎
What, you don't want that job?
不不  我當然想要
No, no, o-of course I do.
我是說  誰會拒絕這樣的機會  是吧
I mean, who wouldn't, right?
這是家大律所
It's a huge firm.
你再也不用在霍華德手下受氣
You get out ‭from under Howard's thumb.
是啊  就是
Right. Exactly.
而且  反正我在哈姆林麥吉爾聯合律所
Besides, HHM is looking more and more like
越來越沒有前途
a dead end for me, anyway.
就是啊  所以還有什么問題嗎
Exactly. So what's the problem?
我只是
I just...
我也不知道
I don't know.
我一直在想你漂在那個池子里的場景
I keep thinking of you floating in that pool.
你知道你想要什么  可我成了你的障礙
You knew what you wanted, but I got in the way.
你說什么呢
What are you talking about?
你進戴維斯梅因律所是為了我
You took the Davis & Main job because of me.
我去那里工作是因為這是正確的選擇
I took that job because it was the right decision.
穩定的收入  有了
A steady paycheck -- done.
比原來不知道大到哪里去的住處  也有了
A place to live that's more than, oh, 5 square feet -- boom.
純色的汽車  到手了
A car that's all one color -- nailed it.
我日子很好過
‭I'm good.
我得到了我想要的
I got what I wanted.
而你  等你進了那什么斯韋卡特
And you, ‭with the Schweikart thing?
你就可以得到你想要的一切
You could have ‭everything you ever wanted.
還有什么不滿意的
What's not to love about that?
是啊
Yeah.
還有什么不滿意的
What's not to love?
人人留學——開啟單向收費新時代
英、澳、日三國免費辦理
眾多美國大學，快捷錄取
人人留學【免費辦理】
震撼上線，趕快登陸
www.rrliuxue.com